const e="english",o=200,a=75,t=[{id:1,question:" He put…………..  eggs in a basket.",option:{a:"white dozen eggs ",b:"a dozen white eggs  ",c:" a white dozen eggs ",d:"dozen white"},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:2,question:"The reason why he was not offered admission was …………… his results could not be found.",option:{a:"that   ",b:"when  ",c:"owing to ",d:"because "},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:3,question:"Course………….  writers are to reflect local colour",option:{a:" material's ",b:"materials'",c:"materials ",d:"material "},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:4,question:"If you saw the photograph of the man……………………you be able to identify him?",option:{a:"could",b:"would   ",c:"can ",d:"will "},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:5,question:"As Obande does not know anyone in this city, he hopes that some kind …………  will put him up for the night",option:{a:"man",b:"men ",c:"inhabitants ",d:"individuals"},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:6,question:" The doctor asked the patient what………….",option:{a:"The problem is   ",b:" Is your problem ",c:"The problem was. ",d:" Is the problem"},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:7,question:"The woman is one? of the …………. of the society.",option:{a:"elitist  ",b:" elites ",c:"ellte",d:"elitists "},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:8,question:`Three quarters of the people in the village  killed but only half of then 
          huts……. affected  
`,option:{a:"were/ were ",b:"was/was",c:"were/ was",d:"was/were "},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:9,question:"The armed robbers went into the house and robbed the three",option:{a:"woman occupants",b:"women's occupants ",c:"woman's occupants",d:"   women occupants."},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:10,question:" It was a free-for-all and the students were blamed for taking the law",option:{a:"in their own hands ",b:"into their own hands ",c:"into their hands ",d:"in their hands."},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:11,question:"The candidate's charisma should be a..………factor in winning the election. ",option:{a:"determinant ",b:"determinate",c:"determining ",d:"determinable "},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:12,question:"I can't stand people prying into my private life. 'Ladi said '………… agree Agbenu",option:{a:"Me too ",b:"Likewise myself ",c:"Me neither ",d:"I also "},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:13,question:" Four weeks ..................  enough for the police to  conclude   their",option:{a:"were",b:" is ",c:" are ",d:" has been"},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:14,question:"  It is bad to take………… property without permission. ",option:{a:"someone else's ",b:"someone’s else",c:" someone's ",d:"someone's else's' "},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:15,question:"Classmate……………………….  I haven't seen for years, wrote to me last week.",option:{a:"whose ",b:"which ",c:"that",d:" whom"},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:16,question:"If you would do me this favour,  I …………..  be very grateful",option:{a:"should",b:" would ",c:" shall ",d:"will"},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:17,question:"Ali plays ……….violin with remarkable skill",option:{a:"a    ",b:"the",c:"their ",d:"some "},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:18,question:"1 have the ……… of meeting the President.",option:{a:"privilege  ",b:"privelege ",c:"previlege ",d:"privilege "},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:19,question:"The sergeant spoke to me in a ……………  manner",option:{a:"Coarse",b:"causal     ",c:"coerce    ",d:"course "},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:20,question:"Idakwo ran……………. miss the train",option:{a:"lest he may",b:" lest ha should",c:"lest he almost   ",d:"lest he will "},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:21,question:"How is the new editor ……………on with hit work",option:{a:"moving",b:"getting",c:"pushing ",d:"going"},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:22,question:"  Be careful not to…………….  this money ",option:{a:"loose  ",b:" loss ",c:" lost",d:" loss"},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:23,question:"Nowadays, many graduates are not Will disposed to teaching……………..",option:{a:"are they",b:"aren't they?",c:"do they?    ",d:" they are?"},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:24,question:"Adike ………….. a message from the club regularly.",option:{a:"Receive ",b:" had received ",c:" receive",d:" has received "},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:25,question:"It is often……. that inflation ……….  from too much money chasing very few goods.    ",option:{a:"said/results",b:"say/result      ",c:"said/result   ",d:"say/ resulted"},section:"most appropriate option",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:26,question:"",option:{a:"spot    ",b:"Law   ",c:"North ",d:"naught "},section:"choose the option that has a different vowel sound from the others.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:27,question:"",option:{a:"cost    ",b:"won’t    ",c:"hope    ",d:"coast "},section:"choose the option that has a different vowel sound from the others.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:28,question:"",option:{a:"there   ",b:"dear    ",c:"fair         ",d:"bear"},section:"choose the option that has a different vowel sound from the others.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:29,question:"",option:{a:"wife",b:"of",c:"off",d:"laugh"},section:"choose the option that has a different consonant sound from the others.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:30,question:"",option:{a:"chef",b:"chief",c:"shoe",d:"ocean"},section:"choose the option that has a different consonant sound from the others.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:31,question:"If he went to London, he would see the Queen",option:{a:"He did not go to London and did not see the Queen",b:" He would like to see the Queen when he goes to London",c:"When he goes to London, he will see the Queen ",d:"He did not see the queen when he went to London."},section:"that best explains the information conveyed ",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:32,question:"Ngozi has always considered her father to be an impassioned man ",option:{a:"Her father is a very strict man  ",b:"Her father is a very lively man ",c:"Her father is an emotional man ",d:"Her father is a disciplined man "},section:"that best explains the information conveyed ",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:33,question:"The manager paid us in hard currency  ",option:{a:"We were paid in a strong and stable currency ",b:"We were paid in new notes ",c:"We were paid in new notes",d:"We were paid in foreign currency."},section:"that best explains the information conveyed ",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:34,question:"The elders rebuked ",option:{a:"Olu for talking issue with his principal. ",b:"Olu was scolded for acting in collusion with his principal ",c:"Olu was reprimanded for arguing with his principal",d:"Olu was blamed for issuing a statement denying his principal."},section:"that best explains the information conveyed ",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:35,question:"In spite of his humble beginning, Audu now throws his weight around ",option:{a:"His noble birth notwithstanding, Audu is a corrupt man ",b:"From his poor background, Audu is now a rich man ",c:"Despite his obvious poverty, Audu is a proud man ",d:"Audu is arrogant despite his simple upbringing ."},section:"that best explains the information conveyed ",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:36,question:" <u>Ch</u>alet",option:{a:"chairman",b:"College",c:"champagne",d:"Chemical"},section:"choose the option that has the same consonant sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined.  ",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:37,question:"Tee<u>th</u>",option:{a:"taught",b:"tank",c:"though",d:"thought"},section:" choose the option that has the same consonant sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:38,question:"Co<u>n</u>crete ",option:{a:"anxious ",b:"concern ",c:" consider ",d:"attend "},section:" choose the option that has the same consonant sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:39,question:"He is well known for his <i>inordinate</i> ambition ",option:{a:"passionate ",b:"sound ",c:"excessive",d:"moderate "},section:"opposite in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics ",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:40,question:"A <i>conservative</i> estimate put the number of missing persons at forty.",option:{a:"an accurate ",b:"An incorrect ",c:"A rough ",d:"Primitive "},section:"opposite in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics ",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:41,question:"Agbenu was <i>ecstatic</i> about her result ",option:{a:"sad",b:"dispassionate ",c:"mad ",d:"pessimistic "},section:"opposite in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics ",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:42,question:"Students could be <i>timid</i>",option:{a:"Pugnacious ",b:"friendly ",c:"bold ",d:"covetous"},section:"opposite in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics ",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:43,question:"The labour leader’s <i>recalcitrant</i> stance was applauded ",option:{a:"flexible ",b:"uncompromising ",c:"well-informed ",d:"stubborn "},section:"opposite in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics ",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:44,question:"The company has continued to <i>monopolize</i> the distribution of the products.",option:{a:"regularize ",b:"liberalize ",c:"centralize ",d:"specialize "},section:"opposite in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics ",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:45,question:"The doctor examined the patient <i>painstakingly</i> ",option:{a:"Carefully ",b:"Perfunctorily ",c:"Professionally ",d:"Painfully "},section:"opposite in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics ",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:46,question:"Toyin is married to an <i>impatient, self-centred man ",option:{a:"a tolerant ",b:"a tolerable",c:"a fretful ",d:"an edgy"},section:"opposite in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics ",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:47,question:"The agency has sworn to deal  with all the <i>apostles</i>  of confederation ",option:{a:"opponents ",b:"apostates ",c:"Proponents ",d:"Protagonists "},section:"opposite in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics ",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:48,question:"The members of the congregation were <i>inspired</i> by the sermon ",option:{a:"enthralled ",b:"disenchanted ",c:"disoriented ",d:"bewitched "},section:"opposite in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics ",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:49,question:"<i>Gregarious</i> animals can be found in the zoo.",option:{a:"lonely ",b:"tame ",c:"wild ",d:"various "},section:"opposite in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics ",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:50,question:"I am <i>loath</i> to do the assignment ",option:{a:"unwilling ",b:"waiting ",c:"dying ",d:"willing "},section:"opposite in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics ",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:51,question:"Only those who are <i>gullible</i> fall victim to his trickery ",option:{a:"astute ",b:"Courteous ",c:"saucy ",d:"devastated"},section:"opposite in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics ",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:52,question:"A cool bath in a hot weather can be truly <i>invigorating</i> ",option:{a:"debilitating ",b:"devastating ",c:"disgusting ",d:"unpalatable"},section:"opposite in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics ",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:53,question:"The witness decided to <i>conceal</i> the evidence ",option:{a:"waive ",b:"divulge ",c:"hide",d:"destroy "},section:"opposite in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics ",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:54,question:"The President SPOKE to the press ",option:{a:"Did the Present write to the press?",b:"Did the president speak to the press?",c:"Who spoke to the press?",d:"Are these the pressmen that the President spoke to?"},section:"word in capital letters has the emphatic stress. Choose the option to which the sentence relates.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:55,question:"My MOTHER served rice and fresh fish stew for dinner.",option:{a:"Did your mother serve rice and fresh fish stew for lunch?",b:"Who served rice and fresh fish stew for dinner?",c:"What kind of meal did your mother serve for dinner?",d:"what kind of meal did your mother serve for dinner? "},section:"word in capital letters has the emphatic stress. Choose the option to which the sentence relates.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:56,question:"Mark<u>e</u>t  ",option:{a:"mortgage ",b:" bachelor ",c:" get ",d:" enter "},section:"choose the option that has the same vowel sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:57,question:"c<u>olo</u>nel ",option:{a:" golden",b:" girl",c:" colony ",d:" goal "},section:"choose the option that has the same vowel sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:58,question:"t<u>e</u>nd ",option:{a:"caned ",b:" jeopardy ",c:"turned ",d:" earned "},section:"choose the option that has the same vowel sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:59,question:"The boys knew that a storm was <i>imminent</i>",option:{a:"Impending ",b:"encroaching ",c:"possible ",d:"threatening "},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:60,question:"The leader has the <i>unstinting</i> support of his party ",option:{a:"cautious ",b:"uninspiring ",c:"unsparing ",d:"laudable "},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:61,question:"The <i>essence</i> of governance is to seek the good and well-being of the majority of the people ",option:{a:"characteristics ",b:"importance ",c:"Secret ",d:"Goal"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:62,question:"The carpenter built a <i>commodious</i> wardrobe ",option:{a:"wide ",b:"gigantic ",c:"small ",d:"spacious"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:63,question:"The company is to <i>shed</i> three thousand staff this year ",option:{a:"Throw up ",b:"placate ",c:"lay off",d:"demote "},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:64,question:"A few years ago, nobody would have believed that the economy would <i>turn around </i>",option:{a:"change ",b:"deteriorate ",c:"improve ",d:"stagnate "},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:65,question:"The man’s story sounded <i>plausible</i> to his audience ",option:{a:"credible ",b:"entertaining ",c:"fantastic ",d:"credulous "},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:66,question:"Before announcing his retirement, Ochima resolved to <i>settle an account with</i> the bank.",option:{a:"get  back at ",b:"pay back all he owes ",c:"close his account with ",d:"retire his loans from "},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:67,question:"He shared his room with a person whose behaviour was quite <i>nauseating</i> ",option:{a:"disgusting ",b:"disrespectful ",c:"disagraceful ",d:"discouraging "},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:68,question:"From what she said, one may <i>infer</i> that she does not like the course",option:{a:"agree ",b:"deduce ",c:"suppose ",d:"realize "},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:69,question:"The party supporters <i>vilified</i> the Chairman for the role he played in the crisis that rocked the party ",option:{a:"impeached ",b:"condemned ",c:"challenged ",d:"elected"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:70,question:"Publishing as a business venture has become a <i>hot potato</i> in Nigeria. ",option:{a:"unacceptable  ",b:"unpleasant ",c:"expensive                                                              ",d:"profitable"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:71,question:"The <i>cynics</i>  feared that the nation’s nascent democracy would fail",option:{a:"illusionists",b:"pessimists",c:"delinquents",d:"critics"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:72,question:"The nurse was in favour of <i>voluntary eutheanasia</i>",option:{a:"a sleeping pill",b:"a major operation",c:"a painless death",d:"a simple operation"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:73,question:"There was a <i>glut</i> of oil on the market",option:{a:"an abundance of",b:"an increase in",c:"a variety of",d:"an accumulation of"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:74,question:"Typist",option:{a:"refuse  (noun)",b:"superb",c:"propose",d:"rebel (verb)"},section:"choose the option that has the same stress pattern as the given word.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:75,question:"Cement",option:{a:"perfect (adjective)",b:"include",c:"interest",d:"employ(noun)"},section:"choose the option that has the same stress pattern as the given word.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2003",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"}],s={subject:e,status:200,total:75,data:t};export{t as data,s as default,o as status,e as subject,a as total};
